Hi, everyone. This is EYA on EYA
Censored Supernatural Bible Changes on
YouTube.
Today is the 14th of March, 2026.
I've been working on a project for you.
I hope you really like it. I hope it
will be of great benefit for you as
you're doing your research on what
scripture is teaching today. Now, if
you're new to my channel, I cover what's
happening to our precious once beloved
Bibles. Our Bibles are under satanic
siege, supernaturally changing, and the
changes are retroactive.
This is my website, bible-changes.com.
I have not updated in a long while. I've
just been really busy,
but it does have some good resources for
you. Now, today I just added a really
great research tool for those of you who
are interested. On my website, in the
search bar, you'll see search examples
of changes in KJV Bible. If you click on
it,
it takes you to a KJV Bible Word Index
with um links to um my website, my
YouTube channel, and my um my books on
Amazon about the Bible changes.
And it is a search engine. Now, it is
not comprehensive with the Bible
changes. But what I've done is I've
taken a list of the new words that I
had, and I created a spreadsheet. I
don't want to go into many technical um
technical um language, but I had this
information in a spreadsheet. I wrote
out all the scripture verses, not all of
them, related to the words, but I gave
examples. And then what I did is that I
created this tool
using I'll tell you, I used Claude. So,
I just did it within the last 24 hours.
I went ahead, and you can see that you
can see the list of new words that are
in the Bible. You can actually type in a
word. Say if you want to look up the
word castles, I can write it in in the
search engine here, press okay, and it
pops up in two verses in the King James
Bible, that's plural. There's There's
castle singular and in castles plural in
the King James Bible now, Genesis 25:16
and Numbers 31:10.
And I'm going to read these to you
because I think you should be able to
hear and see the changes. These are the
sons of Ishmael, and these are their
names by their towns and by their
castles, 12 princes according to their
nations. That's right. Ishmael, the
illegitimate son
of Abraham, is now
now have
castles, and they're 12 princes. How
ridiculous is that?
Ishmael was illegitimate, but now in
scripture, he's now legitimate because
Abraham married um his mother.
Go take a look. The story has changed.
Numbers 31:10 says this, "And they burnt
all their cities wherein they dwell and
all their goodly castles." That's right,
goodly castles with fire.
These verses are obviously changed, and
you're going to see, like you can see in
these two verses, many of these verses I
have indexed have more than one change
in it.
Um again, our Bibles are satanically
changing, and the changes are obvious.
Let me go ahead and give you another
example. The word A, but I'm actually
going to look up the word apron
because now we see that um Adam and Eve
are now wearing aprons in the book of
Genesis. How crazy is that?
In Genesis 3:7,
"And the eyes of them both were opened,
and they knew that they were naked, and
they sewed fig leaves together and made
themselves aprons.
That's right. Adam and Eve now wear
aprons in the Bible.
Again, there are thousands of satanic
changes to scripture. It is not God
changing scripture cuz it's impossible
for him to lie.
But please take a look at this. I think
it'll be useful for you in explaining
what's happening to our Bibles. It's
really obvious and those who have eyes
to see
will indeed see and it's time to wake up
in Jesus' name. Jesus Christ is king of
kings, lord of lords. He is the one true
God. He's the alpha and the omega, the
beginning and the end. And our Bibles
are satanically changing. He is the word
of God and the word of God is forever
settled in heaven.
Our Bibles, our printed Bibles, our
audio Bibles, and our digital Bibles are
all under satanic siege.
Wake up in Jesus' name. Let me know what
you think of these this resource and by
the grace of God I hope to get some
other resources out to you
in the near future. God bless you.